<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Haaukins Documentation on</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Haaukins Documentation on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Binary</title><link>/docs/challenges/binary/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/challenges/binary/</guid><description>Binary Difficulty Levels Bittit Account Recovery Set User ID Format String Exploitation CorROPtion, please! Shrunk-Chunk Heap Overflow Binary Binary exploitation is the process of subverting a compiled application such that it violates some trust boundary in a way that is advantageous to the attacker. It comes down by abusing vulnerabilities that corrupt memory in software or by finding a vulnerability in the program and exploiting it in order to escalate privileges.</description></item><item><title>Configuration</title><link>/docs/haaukins/configuration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/haaukins/configuration/</guid><description>Configuration Files and directory structure config.yml exercises.yml frontends.yml IP Tables Configuration Configuration This page describes the process of configuring a host for running the Haaukins daemon, hknd. The daemon has only been tested on a Linux host with systemd, but binaries for other operating systems can be build as well.
For the remainder of the Wiki, we assume a user hknd user exists with home directory /home/hknd.</description></item><item><title>Connected Services</title><link>/docs/haaukins/connected-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/haaukins/connected-services/</guid><description>Haaukins is using few services to operate its ordinary workload. There are three different services which Haaukins is using namely, haaukins-store, haaukins-exercises, haaukins-webclient.
Haaukins Webclient This is NOT a mandatory service for Haaukins to work. It is implementation of CLI on web, it is using Envoy Proxy with gRPC. Detailed information regarding to it and source code can be found following link here: haaukins-webclient
Haaukins Store This is a service which is using PostreSQL with gRPC.</description></item><item><title>Cryptography</title><link>/docs/challenges/cryptography/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/challenges/cryptography/</guid><description>Cryptography Difficulty Levels JS Crypto Client MD5 Collision Course Lurking in the shadows SSH Vigenère Vignette Cryptography The main goal is usually to crack or clone cryptographic objects or algorithms to reach the flag.
Difficulty Levels The levels of difficulty scale is based on the number of steps required in order to solve the Training Challenge
Very Easy​: It requires just one step in order to get the flag Easy:​ It requires one-two steps, it is based on the challenge category Medium​: It requires two-three steps, it is based on the challenge category Hard: ​It requires three-four steps based on the challenge category Very Hard:​ It requires several steps in order to get the flag JS Crypto Client Points: ​ 10 Difficulty: Easy</description></item><item><title>Forensics</title><link>/docs/challenges/forensics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/challenges/forensics/</guid><description>Forensics Difficulty Levels Network sniffing Web server login Network scanning SSHtay HYDRAted Telnet Stream and Login Git logs FTP server login Man in the Middle Steganography Doormat Steganography Steganography Slam Linux walk-through Translator Android Permission Abuse Android Phishing Login Page Man in the Middle Steganography Doormat Steganography Steganography Slam Linux walk-through Translator Android Permission Abuse Android Phishing Login Page Forensics This is a broad category that includes different types of training challenges such as file format analysis, steganography, memory dump analysis, or network packet capture analysis.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>/docs/haaukins/installation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/haaukins/installation/</guid><description>Server Installation Configuration files and directory structure Systemd Configuration Client Installation Linux and OSX Globally Locally Troubleshooting Windows Globally Locally Rest of the installation (environment variables) CLI Format Guideline Format Entities Actions Arguments Identifiers Examples Server Installation This page describes the process of configuring a host for running the Haaukins daemon, hknd. The daemon has only been tested on a Linux host with systemd, but binaries for other operating systems can be build as well.</description></item><item><title>Introduction</title><link>/docs/haaukins/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/haaukins/introduction/</guid><description>Haaukins is a highly accessible and automated virtualization platform for security education, it has three main components (Docker, Virtualbox and Golang), the communication and orchestration between the components managed using Go programming language. The main reason of having Go environment to manage and deploy something on Haaukins platform is that Go’s easy concurrency and parallelism mechanism. Want to get more insight about architecture of Haaukins visit architecture page
Our primary aim to involve anyone who desire to learn capturing the flag concept in cyber security which is widely accepted approach to learn how to find vulnerability on a system.</description></item><item><title>Reverse Engineering</title><link>/docs/challenges/reverse-engineering/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/challenges/reverse-engineering/</guid><description>Reverse Engineering Difficulty Levels Weird Code Conditional Reverse Engineering Reverse APK PWN_strings C0ffee 0verfl0w Reverse Engineering It is typically the process of taking a compiled (machine code, bytecode) program and converting it back into a more human readable format.
Difficulty Levels The levels of difficulty scale is based on the number of steps required in order to solve the Training Challenge
Very Easy​: It requires just one step in order to get the flag Easy:​ It requires one-two steps, it is based on the challenge category Medium​: It requires two-three steps, it is based on the challenge category Hard: ​It requires three-four steps based on the challenge category Very Hard:​ It requires several steps in order to get the flag Weird Code Points: ​ 25 Difficulty: Easy</description></item><item><title>Starters</title><link>/docs/challenges/starters/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/challenges/starters/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Testing</title><link>/docs/haaukins/testing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/haaukins/testing/</guid><description>Please stick to using Go&amp;rsquo;s testing package conventions.
Before using any third party libraries for testing, please make sure they are strictly necessary.
For integration tests, use the practice described here.
TLDR: Use go test -short ./... (unit tests only) mostly. Use go test ./... for full testing suite (including integration tests).</description></item><item><title>Web Exploitation</title><link>/docs/challenges/web-exploitation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/challenges/web-exploitation/</guid><description>Web Exploitation
Difficulty Levels SQL Injections SQL Injection SQL Users SQL Easy Micro CMS XXS , URL and robots Heartbleed Exposed Logging Login Blogging Cross-Site Request Forgery Phishing Convince visitation of URL Impersonate colleague Abuse Credentials Hijack Domain Cross-Site Scripting Unauthenticated ​Access Remote Access Bust-N-Crack JWT Deeplink
Web Exploitation This category includes all the challenges that provide a vulnerable website, from the ones that contains a bug to the ones that run over an old version of a framework.</description></item><item><title>A Challenge Struct</title><link>/docs/challenges/challenge-struct/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:26:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>/docs/challenges/challenge-struct/</guid><description>Repository title Describe what the challenge is about, any relevant CVE&amp;rsquo;s, which tools should be used for the challenge, etc.
Domain name If the challenge does not have NMAP as a part of the challenge, the general rule of thumb is, that it should have a domain name. This is to easily distinguish challenges from each other when there is a lot of them running on the platform. The domain name should then also be included in the challenge description(s) for the user to easily access the challenge.</description></item><item><title>How to Create A Challenge</title><link>/docs/challenges/how-to-create-chal/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:26:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>/docs/challenges/how-to-create-chal/</guid><description>Creating a Challenge A challenge is created as a subfolder in its category folder. A sample challenge folder is sample/piece_of_pie/ with the contents below:
example/challenge_1/ |-- README.md |-- Dockerfile |-- .gitlab-ci.yml |-- tests `-- test_exploit.py |-- sol/ | `-- exploit.py |-- config (or src) / |-- auto.conf |-- init.sh As above, the challenge folder must have: * The challenge folder should contain following information and main README.md file. You can follow Challenge Repository Structure for an example of how the readme file should be setup for your challenge;</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting Haaukins</title><link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/</guid><description>In this guideline, the way of handling troubles and possible reasons of troubles will be explained with some solutions.
The issues that you may face during active usage of Haaukins
No space left on device VM Import failed Import VM failed due to no space Create data folder for each user on the system Config file not found Guacamole 500 Error Pool overlaps with other one on this address space Prune System Prune volumes Unable to create database client Certificate Issue Issues which can be seeing in setting up development environment</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 19:25:12 +0200</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>user=&#34;cyber&#34;,domain=&#34;es.aau.dk&#34;,document.write(user+&#34;@&#34;+domain);cyber at es.aau.dk</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 19:23:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>/privacy-policy/</guid><description>TLDR: We only use required cookies (session cookie) and we do not collect any personal data.
Website visitors No personal information is collected. No information is stored in the browser. No information is shared with, sent to or sold to third-parties. No information is shared with advertising companies. No information is mined and harvested for personal and behavioral trends. No information is monetized. Contact us Contact us if you have any questions.</description></item></channel></rss>