<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Haaukins on</title><link>/docs/haaukins/</link><description>Recent content in Haaukins on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/haaukins/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configuration</title><link>/docs/haaukins/configuration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/haaukins/configuration/</guid><description>Configuration Files and directory structure config.yml exercises.yml frontends.yml IP Tables Configuration Configuration This page describes the process of configuring a host for running the Haaukins daemon, hknd. The daemon has only been tested on a Linux host with systemd, but binaries for other operating systems can be build as well.
For the remainder of the Wiki, we assume a user hknd user exists with home directory /home/hknd.</description></item><item><title>Connected Services</title><link>/docs/haaukins/connected-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/haaukins/connected-services/</guid><description>Haaukins is using few services to operate its ordinary workload. There are three different services which Haaukins is using namely, haaukins-store, haaukins-exercises, haaukins-webclient.
Haaukins Webclient This is NOT a mandatory service for Haaukins to work. It is implementation of CLI on web, it is using Envoy Proxy with gRPC. Detailed information regarding to it and source code can be found following link here: haaukins-webclient
Haaukins Store This is a service which is using PostreSQL with gRPC.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>/docs/haaukins/installation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/haaukins/installation/</guid><description>Server Installation Configuration files and directory structure Systemd Configuration Client Installation Linux and OSX Globally Locally Troubleshooting Windows Globally Locally Rest of the installation (environment variables) CLI Format Guideline Format Entities Actions Arguments Identifiers Examples Server Installation This page describes the process of configuring a host for running the Haaukins daemon, hknd. The daemon has only been tested on a Linux host with systemd, but binaries for other operating systems can be build as well.</description></item><item><title>Introduction</title><link>/docs/haaukins/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/haaukins/introduction/</guid><description>Haaukins is a highly accessible and automated virtualization platform for security education, it has three main components (Docker, Virtualbox and Golang), the communication and orchestration between the components managed using Go programming language. The main reason of having Go environment to manage and deploy something on Haaukins platform is that Go’s easy concurrency and parallelism mechanism. Want to get more insight about architecture of Haaukins visit architecture page
Our primary aim to involve anyone who desire to learn capturing the flag concept in cyber security which is widely accepted approach to learn how to find vulnerability on a system.</description></item><item><title>Testing</title><link>/docs/haaukins/testing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/haaukins/testing/</guid><description>Please stick to using Go&amp;rsquo;s testing package conventions.
Before using any third party libraries for testing, please make sure they are strictly necessary.
For integration tests, use the practice described here.
TLDR: Use go test -short ./... (unit tests only) mostly. Use go test ./... for full testing suite (including integration tests).</description></item></channel></rss>